Filip Lee

Kockendal

Information Technology Student



CONTACT

Gothenburg, Sweden

(+46) 70 302 53 46

filip.kockendal@gmail.com

PROFILE

Hardworking student aiming at gaining experience and knowledge in the IT field. Experienced in sales and providing excellent customer service. Often described by friends and colleagues as positive, responsible and competent. Quick learner with strong social and analytical skill driven by challenges. Welcoming all opportunities that encourage self-development in a stimulating environment.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- Design Thinking
- Figma
- · HTML/CSS
- Python
- · Google's G Suite
- · Driving License

LANGUAGES

- · Swedish Mother tongue
- English Fluent
- · Chinese Fluent

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

> University of Gothenburg Cognitive Science 2020 - 2023

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA IN TECHNOLOGY

Aranäsgymnasiet Technical Science 2017 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

O SHOP ASSISTANT | JUN. 2020 - PRESENT

FINE LITTLE DAY

Working part-time in a lifestyle design company overseeing store operations

- Responsible for in-store sales, customer service and product display
- · Help packing online orders
- Collecting customer feedback and analysing customer behaviour
- POSTMAN | SEP. 2019 JAN. 2020; APR JUN. 2020
 POSTNORD

Worked full time as a postman

- · Sorted and delivered mail and packages
- Categorised incoming parcels
- Organised packet distribution

RESTAURANT ASSISTANT | APR - SEP. 2019; MAY - AUG. 2021

LISEBERG

Summer job at the restaurant Skeppsmagasinet in an amusement park

- · Worked at the cash register
- · Served drinks at the bar
- · Prepared food and washed dishes

MARKETING MANAGER | AUG. 2017 - JUN. 2018 MATTEGENIETUF

Started a tutoring company through young entrepreneurs program and responsible for marketing strategies, communication as well as tutoring maths